Girls Frontline Assistant Version 10.0 by YusatsuNao

Greetings //
Welcome everyone,
If you love Girls Frontline and want your favourite T-Doll in your desktop you can use this skins. It's all voiced and also have a text for it. For now the text is only in Japanese ( maybe I will fix it later and change to english ) and if your favourite doll is not in the list you can request it by comment and requst on my Deviantart page. Enjoy and have a nice day!

NOTES //
I don't own all resources I just design it and write the code, all Images and Audio are copyrighted to their respective owners. Creative Commons BY-NC-SA 3.0 LICENSE

Creator & Contributor //
Base Design and Code : https://deviantart.com/yusatsunao
Dialogue Synchronization Fixer : https://www.reddit.com/user/Cubic_Corvust

Features // as Version 8.0
// 42 Voiced T-Dolls and Oath Indicator
→ Left click displayed T-Doll to see the dialogue and hear the voice lines
→ Right click displayed T-Doll to hear the voice effect

// 5 Color Themes
→ Game Base Color ( Orange, Green, Blue )
→ Added color ( Red, Purple )
→ Customizeable color theme ( by inputing rgb color codes and press enter, rgb color codes examples "151,102,512" 11 charactes only)

// Profile
→ Your Username
→ Experience Level
→ Experience Points
→ T-Doll Level
→ T-Doll Skill Level

// Settings
→ Username, Level, T-Doll Level / Skill Level Editor
→ Shortcut title and directory Editor
→ Screen Height Config and Taskbar config ( to edit T-Doll height logo position )

// To Do List ( open extended menu and click Check Button )
→ Maximum 5 list is displayable and cuztomizable

// Advanced Settings
→ Graph Display ( default : enabled )
→ Base Indicator ( default : enabled )
→ Network Indicator ( default : disabled )
→ Drive to monitor ( default : C )
→ User Database ( Advanced users only! Please don't open it if you don't know how the skins works )
→ T-Doll Database ( Advanced users only! Please don't open it if you don't know how the skins works )

// System Monitor
→ Clock, Date and Day
→ CPU, RAM, Battery, Network, Drive Status ( You can change what drive you want to monitor, default is C )
→ CPU / RAM Graph
→ Internet Indicator ( Download only )
→ Battery Indicator
→ USER IP / SSID

// Customizable User Data
→ Username
→ User Level
→ T-Doll Level 
→ T-Doll Skill Level
→ Mod Status
→ Oath Status
→ Color Theme
→ Drive Monitoring
→ Application Shortcut
